1. FAQ

1.1. Wood firmware supports only clean decrypted or encrypted roms. Check you rom using no-intro.org nintendo ds dat before reporting bugs.
1.2. Any bugreport must contain save file (except case then problem happens not far from start) and detailed description how reproduce problem. "game 'xxx' sometimes freezes" is not bug report.
1.2.1. In wood 1.33 introduced crc32 calculation feature. Any bugreport about problem with games without crc32 ignored now.

2. LICENSES

Copyright (C) 2007 Acekard, www.acekard.com

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in
all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN
THE SOFTWARE.


FatFs module is an open source software to implement FAT file system to
small embedded systems. This is a free software and is opened for education,
research and commercial developments under license policy of following trems.

 Copyright (C) 2011, ChaN, all right reserved.

* The FatFs module is a free software and there is NO WARRANTY.
* No restriction on use. You can use, modify and redistribute it for
  personal, non-profit or commercial product UNDER YOUR RESPONSIBILITY.
* Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice.


Copyright (C) 2005 - 2008
 Michael Noland (joat)
 Jason Rogers (dovoto)
 Dave Murpy (WinterMute)

This software is provided 'as-is', without any express or implied
warranty.  In no event will the authors be held liable for any
damages arising from the use of this software.

Permission is granted to anyone to use this software for any
purpose, including commercial applications, and to alter it and
redistribute it freely, subject to the following restrictions:

1. The origin of this software must not be misrepresented; you
   must not claim that you wrote the original software. If you use
   this software in a product, an acknowledgment in the product
   documentation would be appreciated but is not required.
2. Altered source versions must be plainly marked as such, and
   must not be misrepresented as being the original software.
3. This notice may not be removed or altered from any source
   distribution.


Copyright (c) 2001, 2002 Swedish Institute of Computer Science.
All rights reserved.

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification,
are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:

1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice,
   this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice,
   this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation
   and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
3. The name of the author may not be used to endorse or promote products
   derived from this software without specific prior written permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE AUTHOR ``AS IS'' AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED
WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF
MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT
SHALL THE AUTHOR BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL,
EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT
OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS
INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN
CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING
IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY
OF SUCH DAMAGE.

This file is part of the lwIP TCP/IP stack.

Author: Adam Dunkels <adam@sics.se>


zlib.h -- interface of the 'zlib' general purpose compression library
version 1.2.5, April 19th, 2010

Copyright (C) 1995-2010 Jean-loup Gailly and Mark Adler

This software is provided 'as-is', without any express or implied
warranty.  In no event will the authors be held liable for any damages
arising from the use of this software.

Permission is granted to anyone to use this software for any purpose,
including commercial applications, and to alter it and redistribute it
freely, subject to the following restrictions:

1. The origin of this software must not be misrepresented; you must not
   claim that you wrote the original software. If you use this software
   in a product, an acknowledgment in the product documentation would be
   appreciated but is not required.
2. Altered source versions must be plainly marked as such, and must not be
   misrepresented as being the original software.
3. This notice may not be removed or altered from any source distribution.

Jean-loup Gailly        Mark Adler
jloup@gzip.org          madler@alumni.caltech.edu


The data format used by the zlib library is described by RFCs (Request for
Comments) 1950 to 1952 in the files http://www.ietf.org/rfc/rfc1950.txt
(zlib format), rfc1951.txt (deflate format) and rfc1952.txt (gzip format).
